Capron Family papers, 1777-1950.
Congregational Library & Archives
- Annie Hooker Morse (née Capron), 1865 1909; 1865-1909; 11 Folders
  This series contains the papers of Annie H. Morse (née Capron), daughter of Sarah (née Hooker) and William Capron. The majority of this series contains letters authored by Annie to her immediate family. This series also contains letters from Annie's husband, Lewis K. Morse, and miscellaneous letters sent to Annie.
  - Annie H. Morse (née Capron) certificate, 1865 (Box 2, Folder 72)
  - Annie H. Morse (née Capron) to Sarah B. Capron (née Hooker), 1885 1886; 1885-1886 (Box 2, Folder 73)
  - Annie H. Morse (née Capron) to Laura E. Keith (née Capron), 1885 1886; 1885-1886 (Box 2, Folder 74)
  - Annie H. Morse (née Capron) to Anne E. Tufts (née Hooker), 1886 (Box 2, Folder 75)
  - Annie H. Morse (née Capron) to Laura E. Keith (née Capron), 1904 1906; 1904-1906 (Box 2, Folder 76)
  - Annie H. Morse (née Capron) to Sarah B. Capron (née Hooker), 1906 (Box 2, Folder 77)
  - Annie H. Morse (née Capron) to Anne E. Tufts (née Hooker), 1906 (Box 2, Folder 78)
  - Alice H. Wellington to Annie and Lewis Morse, 1906 (Box 2, Folder 79)
  - Annie H. Morse (née Capron) to Anne E. Tufts (née Hooker), 1908 1909; 1908-1909 (Box 2, Folder 80)
  - Annie H. Morse (née Capron) to Laura E. Keith (née Capron), 1908 1909; 1908-1909 (Box 2, Folder 81)
  - Annie H. Morse (née Capron) to Sarah B. Capron (née Hooker), 1909 (Box 2, Folder 82)
  - Lewis K. Morse to Laura E. Keith (née Capron), 1909 (Box 2, Folder 90)
- Laura Elizabeth Keith (née Capron), 1865 1950; 1865-1950; 18 Folders; 1 Volume
  This series contains the papers of Laura E. Keith (née Capron), daughter of Sarah (née Hooker) and William Capron. The majority of this series contains letters authored by Laura. The series also contains correspondence between members of the Keith family, correspondence from Laura's children, James and Annie, letters from Laura's husband, James D. Keith, and a journal.
  - Miscellaneous American Board of Commissioners for Foreign Missions publications, 1865 1950; 1865-1950 (Box 2, Folder 57)
  - Miscellaneous collected publications, 1871 1906; 1871, 1906 (Box 2, Folder 58)
  - Laura E. Keith (née Capron) to Sarah B. Capron (née Hooker), 1884 (Box 2, Folder 59)
  - Laura E. Keith (née Capron) to Martha V. Hooker (née Chickering), 1885 (Box 2, Folder 60)
  - Laura E. Keith (née Capron) to Anne E. Tufts (née Hooker), 1885 (Box 2, Folder 61)
  - Laura E. Keith (née Capron) to Sarah B. Capron (née Hooker), 1885 1886; 1885-1886 (Box 2, Folder 62)
  - Laura E. Keith (née Capron) diary, 1886 1908; 1886-1908 (Box 1, Volume 11)
  - Correspondence to James W. Keith and John W. Keith, 1890 1894; 1890-1894 (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - James M. Keith and Arthur M. Keith lawsuit correspondence, 1891 1892; 1891-1892 (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - Letters to Laura E. Keith (née Capron), 1904 1906; circa 1904-1906 (Box 2, Folder 63)
  - Laura E. Keith (née Capron) to Anne E. Tufts (née Hooker), 1906 1908; 1906-1908 (Box 2, Folder 64)
  - Annie H. Hart (née Keith) to Laura E. Keith (née Capron), 1906 1909; 1906-1909 (Box 2, Folder 65)
  - James M. Keith to Laura E. Keith (née Capron) and James D. Keith, 1906 (Box 2, Folder 66)
  - James D. Keith to Laura E. Keith (née Capron), 1906 1909; 1906-1909 (Box 2, Folder 67)
  - Laura E. Keith (née Capron) to Annie H. Morse (née Capron), 1909 (Box 2, Folder 68)
  - Letters to Laura E. Keith (née Capron), 1925, undated (Box 2, Folder 69)
  - Dindigal Boarding School recitation hall blueprint, 1927 (Folder 7)
    Separated Materials
    This blueprint was separated from the folder "Correspondence between Laure E. Keith (née Capron) and the American Board of Commissioners for Foreign Missions, 1928-1938" to be safely stored in flat files.
  - Correspondence between Laure E. Keith (née Capron) and the American Board of Commissioners for Foreign Missions, 1928 1938; 1928-1938 (Box 2, Folder 70)
    The "Dindigal Boarding School recitation hall blueprint, 1927" was removed from this folder so that it could be safely stored in the flat files.
  - Laura E. Keith (née Capron) to Sarah B. Capron (née Hooker), undated (Box 2, Folder 71)
- Photographic materials, 1882 1916; 1882-1916; 6 Folders; 2 Volumes
  This series contains photographs and other types of visual media. The majority of the series contains photographs taken in India, likely mostly from Madurai and its environs. This series also contains a series of images from South Africa and an album for the Capron family.
  - India photograph album, 1882 1886; circa 1882-1886 (Box 5, Volume 2)
  - Lucy Perry Noble Bible School tract and photograph, 1914 1916; 1914-1916 (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - Photographs of India, undated (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - Images of India, undated (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - India panorama, undated (Box 5, Folder 6)
  - Images of South Africa, undated (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - Miscellaneous photographs, undated (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - Capron family album, undated (Box 3, Volume 2)